{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Sprinkler Winterization Services","appliedActionRules":{"SDB_SCROLLY_SITE_24719":"SDB_SCROLLY_SITE_24719_ctrl"},"categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/46360/":{"taskOID":46360,"originalTaskOID":46360,"setID":1285,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6285,"questionDisplayText":"Winterize or activate","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Do you want to Winterize or Activate your sprinkler system?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":8470,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Winterize (Blow-out) Sprinklers","answerDisplayText":"Winterize (Blow-out) Sprinklers","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8471,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Activate or Startup Sprinklers","answerDisplayText":"Activate or Startup Sprinklers","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6286,"questionDisplayText":"How many zones does your sprinkler system have?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How many zones does your sprinkler system have?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":8472,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"1 - 4","answerDisplayText":"1 - 4","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8473,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"5 - 8","answerDisplayText":"5 - 8","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8474,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"More than 8","answerDisplayText":"More than 8","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8475,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Don't know","answerDisplayText":"Don't know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6288,"questionDisplayText":"Age of Current System","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How old is your sprinkler system?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":8479,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than 1 year","answerDisplayText":"Less than 1 year","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8481,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"1-3 years","answerDisplayText":"1-3 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8480,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"3-5 years","answerDisplayText":"3-5 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8482,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 5 years","answerDisplayText":"More than 5 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8475,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Don't know","answerDisplayText":"Don't know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6292,"questionDisplayText":"Recurring Service Requested","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Will this request be a recurring service?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":8492,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8493,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6285,"questionDisplayText":"Winterize or activate","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Do you want to Winterize or Activate your sprinkler system?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":8470,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Winterize (Blow-out) Sprinklers","answerDisplayText":"Winterize (Blow-out) Sprinklers","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8471,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Activate or Startup Sprinklers","answerDisplayText":"Activate or Startup Sprinklers","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":8470,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Winterize (Blow-out) Sprinklers","answerDisplayText":"Winterize (Blow-out) Sprinklers","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8471,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Activate or Startup Sprinklers","answerDisplayText":"Activate or Startup Sprinklers","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6286,"questionDisplayText":"How many zones does your sprinkler system have?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How many zones does your sprinkler system have?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":8472,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"1 - 4","answerDisplayText":"1 - 4","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8473,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"5 - 8","answerDisplayText":"5 - 8","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8474,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"More than 8","answerDisplayText":"More than 8","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8475,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Don't know","answerDisplayText":"Don't know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":8472,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"1 - 4","answerDisplayText":"1 - 4","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8473,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"5 - 8","answerDisplayText":"5 - 8","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8474,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"More than 8","answerDisplayText":"More than 8","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8475,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Don't know","answerDisplayText":"Don't know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6288,"questionDisplayText":"Age of Current System","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How old is your sprinkler system?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":8479,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than 1 year","answerDisplayText":"Less than 1 year","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8481,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"1-3 years","answerDisplayText":"1-3 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8480,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"3-5 years","answerDisplayText":"3-5 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8482,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 5 years","answerDisplayText":"More than 5 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8475,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Don't know","answerDisplayText":"Don't know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":8479,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than 1 year","answerDisplayText":"Less than 1 year","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8481,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"1-3 years","answerDisplayText":"1-3 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8480,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"3-5 years","answerDisplayText":"3-5 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8482,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 5 years","answerDisplayText":"More than 5 years","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8475,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Don't know","answerDisplayText":"Don't know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6292,"questionDisplayText":"Recurring Service Requested","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Will this request be a recurring service?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":8492,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8493,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":8492,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8493,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/46360/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":46360,"taskName":"Sprinkler System for Lawn and Garden - Winterize or Activate","taskDescription":"Winterize or Activate a Sprinkler System","xmTaskDescriptor":"Sprinkler Winterization Services","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":231,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Lawn Winterize Spring systems front","textMessagingName":"Winterize Sprinkler","rolloverLongDesc":"Systems consist of buried pipes \u0026 sprinkler heads that pop up when in operation. Winterization prevents damage to these parts, Activation is then required in the Spring.","rolloverShortDesc":"Winterize or Activate Sprinklers.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Winterize or Activate a Lawn and Garden Sprinkler System.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Winterize Sprinkler System \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Activate Sprinklers","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":47,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Sprinkler System - Winterize or Activate","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Lawn and Garden Sprinkler System - Winterize or Activate","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Sprinkler System Project","urlName":"Lawn-and-Garden-Sprinkler-System-Winterize-or-Activate","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Sprinkler System Winterization Pros - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Costs \u0026 Reviews","searchKeywords":"Lawn,Winterize, Winter, Spring, yard,blow-out, out, blow, sprinkler, system,","emcCategoryOid":-12047,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":1285,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"isCookielessUser":true}